<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Home on Peter Zung</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Peter Zung</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Feb 2018 18:56:13 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>ETA Tool</title><link>/projects/creations/etatool/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/creations/etatool/</guid><description>The ETA Tool is a web-app that aims to bring Calgary closer to Vision Zero (Zero casualties due to road traffic) by showing how lower speed limits can save lives while minimally impacting commute lengths. To this end, the web app projects changes in the estimated time of arrival (ETA) for commutes based on changes to speed limits on certain road segments. The tool helps Calgarians to stay better informed on how those speed limit changes would potentially affect their commutes by allowing for Calgarians to input their very own commute starting and end points.</description></item><item><title>Search Results</title><link>/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/search/</guid><description>This file exists solely to respond to /search URL with the related search layout template.
No content shown here is rendered, all content is based in the template layouts/page/search.html
Setting a very low sitemap priority will tell search engines this is not important content.
This implementation uses Fusejs, jquery and mark.js
Initial setup Search depends on additional output content type of JSON in config.toml
[outputs] home = [&amp;quot;HTML&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;JSON&amp;quot;] Searching additional fileds To search additional fields defined in front matter, you must add it in 2 places.</description></item><item><title>UAlberta AugApp</title><link>/projects/creations/augapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/projects/creations/augapp/</guid><description>Developed the AugApp for Android for the University of Alberta. The AugApp is a calendar app that consolidates the events around campus into one bulletin so that students can have easier access to the happenings around campus.</description></item></channel></rss>